wavuti.com 2010-05-23

# Privacy - wavuti

## Read, understand and conform to:  

I. AGREEMENT

Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer or provider. Any material from this site is provided 'AS IS' and 'WYSIWYG', should youencounter any problem with information provided here, 

www.wavuti.com or the owner WILL NOT BEAR ANY RESPONSIBILITY for ANY damage caused.www.wavuti.com cannot be held liable for any kind of damages, whether direct or indirect, resulting from the use of this site or its contents.

If you visit this site, and you like the information, and you use the information, please be careful! When using this site, you agree and accept to NOT take any legal action against this site for contents quoted from another blog or website ESPECIALLY when the link to original content is provided. Links to other sites are provided as a service, but 

www.wavuti.com can not be held responsible for their content(s). Any information that receives complaints will be taken down IMMEDIATELY following an email alert or warning. Please contact the owner of this site as soon as you notice anything published against the proper citation of copyright and acknowledgment.  
  
II. PRIVACY POLICY

www.wavuti.com respects your privacy.  
Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of wavuti.com

External Sites.  
www.wavuti.com is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information or entering any form of agreement. Information provided on this site does not mean it endorse positions or activities of such quoted sites. While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to and from www.wavuti.com  
and you are personally solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any personal information such as but not limited to passwords, date of birth, nationality, citizenship, social security number, credit card information, TIN number, passport number, account information and any other information deemed personal by the legal bodies. In addition, other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through www.wavuti.com have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions. Contact directly the owner of such information for proof of existence, authenticity and any other inquiries or if you have any questions about their privacy policies.   
  
Cookies  
A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows www.wavuti.com to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and www.wavuti.com does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as news feeds.  

III. DISCLOSURE POLICY

This site may accept forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

This site abides by word of mouth marketing standards. We believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity. The compensation received will influence publication time priority i.e. will be published first come first serve, depending on the advertising content, topics or posts made in this site. That content, advertising space or post will be clearly identified as paid or sponsored content.

The owner(s) of this site is not compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. The views and opinions expressed on this site are purely of the site owner and if any content is quoted from another blog or website, a link back to the original content will be provided and honored, webmaster and owners of such contents will be sought permission first unless it was listed under the creative common license or a sharing service provided or anything falling under the 'lawful sharing' category. If I claim or appear to be experts on a certain topic or product or service area, I will only endorse products or services that I believe, based on my expertise and research, are worthy of such endorsement.

IV. TERMS OF USE

Information downloaded from this site can be freely used when proper credit is given, unless the use of such information is in conflict with the law of the user's place of residence.

The articles appearing in this site are collected from various Newspapers, TV Channels, Word of mouth and other sources of information but does not warrant or assume any legal liability or responsibility for the accuracy, completeness or usefulness of the information provided here NOR does this site endorse positions or activities of such quoted sites. 

This is a personal website aimed at sharing various opportunities and news information with the public. It is written, edited and maintained by the site owner.  
For questions about this site, please contact us via the 'Tuwasiliane' contact page.  
  
Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet  
  
All of the above became binding and applicable as of Tuesday, 27th October 2009
